<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Easion</string>

    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab_activity_test">TabActivityTest</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_username">Username</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_username">This username is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing username completions."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tab">TabActivity</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>


    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Alles fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_test_login">Sign in</string>


    <string name="info_tab_1">Parantion develops high end, easy to use online tools to measure all kinds of indicators. Aspects such as satisfaction or happiness of small and large groups of people can be measured by surveys. Also more complicated processes such as benchmarks or panels can be performed with the Parantion Survey tool called Scorion Online Survey.\n\n Parantion also measures progress in personal development. The Scorion questionnaires used in the Scorion platform are available through the Scorion App. \n\nThe most important features of the Scorion platform are: SaaS, Friendly user interface to create forms, Flexibility through the use of the Itembank and the use of all kinds of graphics and statistics on the dashboards. Even in case of large amounts of data and complex processes, you can easily provide a clear view of the Talent Development of students, employees or other professionals. \n\nWith Scorion, you can reach your desired results easy, fast and simple.\n\n\n\n </string>

    <string name="info_tab_header">Personal Talent Development, Assessments and Surveys.</string>

</resources>
